Guide to the Jewish Labor Committee Records, Part III WAG.025.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Officers and Staff Members, 1939-2008
  - Subseries F: Michael Perry, 1966-2005
    - Ethnic Labor Coalition National Meeting, 1985-1987, 1997, undated; 1 folder (Box 456)
    - Jewish Labor Committee - Executive Committee [and Labor Cabinet], 1994-1997; 1 folder (Box 456)
    - Farrakhan, 1985, 1988, 1990, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 456)
    - "FES" Friedrich Ebert Stiftung, 1986-1994; 1 folder (Box 456)
    - Frontlash, 1985-1986, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 456)
    - Greyhound Boycott, 1990; 1 folder (Box 456)
    - Haiti, 1991-1994; 1 folder (Box 456)
    - Hatch Act, 1988-1992; 2 folders (Box 456)
    - Histadrut, 1979, 1985-1997, undated; 3 folders (Box 456)
    - Holocaust, 1978-1983; 1 folder (Box 456)
    - Holocaust Studies, 1985-1989; 1 folder (Box 456)
    - Human Rights, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 456)
    - ILG - Williamsburg [International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union], 1989-1990; 1 folder (Box 456)
    - Immigration, 1985-1992, undated; 3 folders (Box 456)
    - Industrial Homework, 1980, 1986-1990, undated; 2 folders (Box 433)
    - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU), 1969, 1981-1996; 2 folders (Box 472)
    - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU): Mission to Israel, 1986-1990; 5 folders (Box 472)
    - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU): Mission to Israel-- Clippings, 1987-1989; 1 folder (Box 472)
    - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU): Mission to Israel-- Report, 1989; 3 folders (Box 472)
    - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU): Fifteenth World Congress, 1992, 1983, 1988, 1992; 1 folder (Box 472)
    - Israel: Articles on Occupied Territories and International Law, Labor Issues, Military Government in the Territories, etc., 1988, 1991, undated; 2 folders (Box 472)
    - International Unions, 1985-1995; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Iraq, 1990-1991; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Israel: Arms, 1992; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Israel: Arms Sales, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Israel: Boycott, 1989-1991; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Israel: Economy, 1985-1993, 1999; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Israel: Foreign Policy, 1984-1990, undated; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Israel: Image, 1985-1990; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Israel: Labor Support, 1992-1994; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Israel: Loan Guarantees, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Israel: Peace Conference, 1987-1989, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Israel: Politics, 1989-1994; 2 folders (Box 433)
    - Israel: Society, 1992, undated; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Israel: Study Tours, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Israel: United Nations, 1975, 1989
    - Israel: U.S. Relations, 1986-1987, 1990, undated; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Israel: West Bank, 1988-1993; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - West Bank Uprising, 1994, undated; 2 folders (Box 433)
    - Issue Summaries, Undated; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Jewish Federations, 1993; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Jews of Poland, 1987; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Justice for Janitors, 1987, 1993-1996; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Labor Cabinet, 1989-1995; 2 folders (Box 433)
    - Labor: Foreign Policy, 1978, 1986-1996; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Labor: Image, 1969, 1979, 1985-1995; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Labor: Jewish Support, 1988, 1993-1999, 2003; 2 folders (Box 433)
    - Labor: Management Cooperation, Undated; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Labor: Political Action, 1987, 1990, 1992; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Lyndon Larouche, 1983-1987, 1990, 1999; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Los Angeles, CA (JLC), 1984-1996; 2 folders (Box 433)
    - Los Angeles Riots, 1992; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Mailings, 1993, 1996, undated; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Mailing Lists, 1984-1992, undated; 1 folder (Box 433)
    - Marriott, 1987-1996, undated; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Membership Campaign, 1980, 1985-1995, undated; 2 folders (Box 457)
    - Minimum Wage, 1989-1996; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA), 1993, undated; 2 folders (Box 457)
    - National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council (NJCRAC): Marriott Hotel, 1987-1988, undated; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council (NJCRAC): Soviet Jewry, 1990; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council (NJCRAC): Task Forces, Various, 1990-1991; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council (NJCRAC): Women, 1989-1992; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council (NJCRAC): World Jewry, 1992; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - New Jewish Agenda, 1990; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers (OCAW), 1982-1988, undated; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Organizing Media Project, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), 1984-1995; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - "Our Legacy: Jews and the American Labor Movement", 1983, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Owens, Major, 1994; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Palestine Liberation Organization (PLO), 1968, 1985-1993; 3 folders (Box 457)
    - Parental Leave, 1987-1993; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Park 55 Hotel, 1990, undated; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Pay Equity, 1990-1992, undated; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Peace Now, 1982-1996; 2 folders (Box 457)
    - Philadelphia, PA (JLC), 1978-1979, 1990-1998; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Poland: Jewish Community Response, 1981-1983, undated; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Political Action: Labor, 1986-1996; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Pollard, 1991-1995; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Population: Jewish, 1985, 1989; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Poverty, 1992; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Presidents' Conference [Conference of Presidents of Major American Jewish Organizations], 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Press, 1986-1994; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Press in the Middle East, undated; 1 folder (Box 457)
    - Privatization, circa 1993; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Productivity, 1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Progressive Zionist Caucus, circa 1987; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Project Nishma, 1991-1994; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Project South Africa, 1987-1989; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Refugees, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Religion and Labor, 1984-1996; 3 folders (Box 458)
    - Religion: Schools, 1995, undated; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Religious Expression in Public Schools, 1993-1998; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Religious Rights, 1994; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Right to Know, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Right-to-Work, 1979, 1992, undated; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Right Wing Groups, 1987; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Romania, 1989-1993, undated; 2 folders (Box 458)
    - Shell Boycott, 1990; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Slovakia, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Social Democratic Movement, USA, 1993; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Socialist International, 1986-1993; 3 folders (Box 458)
    - South Africa, 1985-1989; 2 folders (Box 458)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1972, 1982-1990, undated; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Striker Replacement, 1990-1995; 3 folders (Box 458)
    - Subminimum Wage, 1985; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Sweatshops, 1989, 1994-1996, undated; 2 folders (Box 472)
    - Trade, 1983-1995, undated; 3 folders (Box 458)
    - Trade: Textile Quotas, 1976-1977, 1981-1988, undated; 1 folder (Box 458)
    - Trade: Textile Quotas, 1976-1977, 1981-1988, undated; 1 folder (Box 455)
    - U.S. Holocaust Museum, 1987-1995; 1 folder (Box 455)
    - Vermont, 1985; 1 folder (Box 455)
    - Yugoslavia, 1989-1995; 2 folders (Box 455)
    - Zim Lines, 1991, 1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 455)
  - Subseries G: Other Officers and Staff Members, 1935-2008
    This series contains the papers of several JLC staff members. Jacob Pat's papers focus on contacts with and aid to Polish Jewish refugees in Europe, Latin America, and Israel. Sydney Bykofsky's scrapbooks, photographs, and awards document his own achievements largely separate from the JLC. A subject file Bykofsky maintained on developments in Central America in the 1980s is also included. Paul Greenberg's papers mainly document the activities of the JLC's Washington, DC chapter, though they also relate to national administration. Finally, Jeanette DiLorenzo's papers document her work with the JLC's Educators' Chapter, but also largely with the United Federation of Teachers.
    Materials are arranged according to their original order.
    - Sydney Bykofsky: Award from the State of Israel Bonds (Oversize), 1996; 1 folder (Box 507)
    - Sydney Bykofsky: Delegate Pin, 1961; 1 item (Box 501)
    - Sydney Bykofsky Papers, 1934-1942, 1965-2002; 7 folders (Box 492)
    - Sydney Bykofsky: Plaque, 1984; 1 item (Box 502)
    - Sydney Bykofsky: Plaques, 1973, 1976, 1979, 1983, 1991; 5 items (Box 500)
    - Sydney Bykofsky: Scrapbook, 1935, 1970-1996, undated; 1 item (Box 501)
    - Jacob Pat Papers, 1957-1963 (Box 248, Folder 25-31)
    - Jacob Pat Papers, 1949-1955; 1 folder (Box 492)
    - Jeanette DiLorenzo Papers (Box 390)
    - Paul Greenberg: Washington, DC-- Organizing Committee, 1995-1997; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Washington, DC-- Membership Lists, 1995; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Charter Schools, 1996; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Campus Campaign, 1996; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Rugmark Campaign, 1995, undated; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Washington, DC-- Programs and Membership, 1994-1996, undated; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Holocaust Museum/Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA), 1996; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Washington, DC-- Religion and Labor, Strategic Planning, etc., 1991-1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Washington, DC-- Membership, Research, and Programs, 1988-1993; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Washington, DC-- Memberhship, Programs, National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council (NJCRAC), etc., 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Washington, DC and General, 1990-1992; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Washington, DC, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Washington, DC-- Membership Letters, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Current Correspondence/Clippings, 1995-1996, undated; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council (NJCRAC), 1995-1996; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Biennial Convention (60th Anniversary), 1993; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: JLC National-- Issues Summaries, 1986, 1988, undated; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Washington, DC-- Executive Committee Notes, 1985-1989, undated; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Washington, DC-- Executive Board, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Washington, DC-- General Materials, Correspondence, 1985-1989; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: JLC National, 1983-1990; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: JLC Local Newsletter and Reports, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Build Union-- General, 1986-1990, undated; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Build Union-- George Washington University Hillel Building, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Build Union-- Holocaust Museum, 1985-1990; 1 folder (Box 391)
    - Paul Greenberg: Selective Service, 1971; 1 folder (Box 391)
- Series IV: Regional Offices and Local Chapters, 1906-2009
  The series mainly contains publicity materials, expense reports, and local correspondence and memoranda generated or collected by the JLC's local leadership, both its main regional offices and its various chapters. The series also includes correspondence between local leadership and the national JLC, as well as activity reports submitted to the national office by the local leadership. The JLC's offices in Boston (the northeast regional office), Chicago, Detroit, Los Angeles (the California regional office), Philadelphia, and Washington, D.C. are particularly well-represented. Herman Brown, longtime director of the JLC Boston/Northeast Region office, was also heavily involved in the Boston district of the Workmen's Circle, and his correspondence, notes, and reports comprise a large portion of both groups' records. The records of the JLC's local chapters and regional offices provide an overview of local labor and anti-discrimination activity. Though the local JLC offices often mirror the national JLC in their campaigns and areas of advocacy, the local records also provide insight into issues specific or of particular importance to the localities represented.
  To a lesser extent, mostly financial material from the Boston branch of the JLC's Workmen's Circle division is also included, as are the records of the United Hebrew Trades (UHT), which became the New York division of the JLC in 1995. The UHT materials are primarily from the 2000s, but of particular note is the UHT's original charter from 1906.
  Records of the regional regional offices and local chapters are listed first, followed by the materials related to the general field staff.
  - Atlanta, GA, 1981-1984 (Box 178, Folder 17)
  - Arizona, 2000-2008; 5 folders (Box 409)
  - Augusta, ME, 1982-1983 (Box 178, Folder 18)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1946-1973, 1979-1980, 1985-1986 (Box 178, Folder 19-28)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1987, 1992; 1 folder (Box 409)
  - Boston, MA, 1945-1949 (Box 178, Folder 29-32)
  - Boston, MA, 1950-1957 (Box 178A)
  - Boston, MA, 1958-1976 (Box 179)
  - Boston, MA, 1977-1989 (Box 180, Folder 1-10)
  - Boston, MA: Monthly Reports, 1957, 1968-1969 (Box 180, Folder 11-12)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region, 1987-1995, undated; 15 folders (Box 409)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region, 1993-2008, undated (Box 410)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Jewish Labor Committee-- New York, Current, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Baltimore, 1977, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Membership, 1962-1968, 1975, undated; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Jewish Labor Committee, Canada-- Report to Biennial Convention, 1975; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Chronological File, 1973-1977; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Press Releases, 1975-1976, undated; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Massachusetts Coalition for Full Employment, 1978, undated; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: 1977 Jewish Labor Committee Human Rights Award Dinner and Other Organizations' Dinners, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Workmen's Circle, 1978; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Memos to Sponsors (Kennedy Dinner), 1973; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Kennedy Dinner-- Letters, 1973; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Kennedy Dinner-- Letters, Copies and Drafts, 1973; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Kennedy Dinner-- News Clips, 1973; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Kennedy Dinner-- Financial, 1973; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Julius Bernstein Dinners, 1969, 1974, undated; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Monthly Financial Report, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Americans for Progressive Israel, 1979, undated; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Bakke, undated; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Combined Jewish Philanthropies, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Labor Law Reform, 1978; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1982, undated; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Past Members, 1978, undated; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Massachusetts State Labor Council, 1978, undated; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: 1982 Jewish Labor Committee Convention, 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: 1979 Jewish Labor Committee Convention, 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Massachusetts Coalition for Human Rights, 1978; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Massachusetts Committee for Full Employment, 1976-1978, undated; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Budget Coalition, 1982; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: List of Labor Leaders, 1986; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Civil Rights Coalition, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Activities, 1982; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Jewish Labor Committee National Office, 1977-1981; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Letters Received, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Jewish Labor Committee NE [Northeast or New England], 1975-1981; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Nunes Affair, 1979; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: New York Legislative Conference, 1982; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Quinn Dinner Press, 1972; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Jewish Labor Committee in Vermont, 1978-1979, undated; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Fund Raising, 1969; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Congressional Responses, 1976; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Brookline Condominium Eviction, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Trade Union Council, 1967-1969; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Labor for a Secure Israel, 1977-1982; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Financial Documents, 1973-1977, undated; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: General, 1986-1994, 1998-1999, undated; 3 folders (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Biennial Convention 1998, 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Burma Sanction Law, 1999; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Coalitions, 1999; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Combined Jewish Philanthropies, 1999; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Connecticut, 1996, 1999-2000; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Contingent Workers Campaign, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Forum-- Cash Balance Pensions, 1999; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Forum-- Health Care: Crisis at the Bedside, 2000; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Fundraising, 1999; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Health Care, 1999; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Israel, 1990-1994, 1999, undated; 2 folders (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Jewish Community Relations Council, 1998-2000; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Labor Support, 1998-2000, undated; 2 folders (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Legislation-- Federal, 1999; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Legislation-- State, 1999; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Living Wage Campaign, 1997-1999, undated; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Maine, 1993, 1997-2000; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Massachusetts AFL-CIO, 1998-2000; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Massachusetts Interfaith Committee for Worker Justice (MICFWJ), 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Massachusetts Interfaith Committee for Worker Justice (MICFWJ)-- Task Force on Sweatshops, 1995-2000, undated; 2 folders (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Massachusetts Interfaith Committee for Worker Justice (MICFWJ)-- Treasurer Reports, 1998-2000; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: National, 1998-2000; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: New Hampshire, 1993, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Newsletter, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Photographs, 1967, 1988-1992, 1997-1998, undated; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Programs, 1996-1999; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Reproductive Hazards in the Workplace, 1983, 1988-1989; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Rhode Island, 1993; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Torah Study Group, 1998-2000; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Vermont, 1993-2000; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Boston, MA/Northeast Region: Welfare to Work, 1999; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Workmen's Circle, Boston District: District Committee, 1989-1994; 2 folders (Box 421)
  - Workmen's Circle, Boston District: Filmmakers, 1989-1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 421)
  - Workmen's Circle, Boston District: Center Papers-- General, 1968, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Workmen's Circle, Boston District: Expenses (National), 1988-1991; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Workmen's Circle, Boston District: District Finances, 1991-1995; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Workmen's Circle, Boston District: Albert E. Marks Yiddish Lecture Series, 1991-1994; 2 folders (Box 411)
  - Workmen's Circle, Boston District: Membership, 1993; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Workmen's Circle, Boston District: Public Affairs, 1990-1994; 2 folders (Box 411)
  - Workmen's Circle, Boston District: Reports, 1986-1994; 4 folders (Box 411)
  - Workmen's Circle, Boston District: Tax Status, 1989; 1 folder (Box 411)
  - Bridgeport, CT, 1945-1954 (Box 180, Folder 13-23)
  - Bridgeport, CT, 1956-1959, 1963 (Box 181, Folder 1-3)
  - Bridgeport, CT: Monthly Reports, 1957 (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1945-1951 (Box 181, Folder 5-21)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1952-1954 (Box 182, Folder 1-7)
  - Buffalo, NY: American Civil Liberties, 1942, 1947-1953 (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - Buffalo, NY: Americans for Democratic Action, 1947 (Box 182, Folder 9)
  - Buffalo, NY: Bell Aircraft/UAW, 1949-1950 (Box 182, Folder 10)
  - Buffalo, NY: B'nai B'rith/ADL, 1946-1954 (Box 182, Folder 11-12)
  - Buffalo, NY: Board of Community Relations, 1954 (Box 182, Folder 13)
  - Buffalo, NY: Bowling Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 182, Folder 14)
  - Buffalo, NY: Committee for Social Action, 1947-1948 (Box 182, Folder 15)
  - Buffalo, NY: Community Relations, 1947-1950 (Box 182, Folder 16-17)
  - Buffalo, NY: Coordinating Committee on Minority Interests, 1949-1953 (Box 182, Folder 18)
  - Buffalo, NY: Films, 1946-1953, undated (Box 182, Folder 19)
  - Buffalo, NY: Housing, 1946, 1948-1952 (Box 182, Folder 20-22)
  - Buffalo, NY: Institute, 1950-1953 (Box 182, Folder 23-26)
  - Buffalo, NY: Kutcher Case, 1949 (Box 182, Folder 27)
  - Buffalo, NY: NCRAC/ADL, etc. Controversy, 1944, 1952-1953 (Box 182, Folder 28)
  - Buffalo, NY: Publicity, 1951 (Box 182, Folder 29)
  - Buffalo, NY: Workmen's Circle, 1949-1950 (Box 182, Folder 30)
  - Chicago, IL, 1945-1949 (Box 182, Folder 31-33)
  - Chicago, IL, 1950-1960 (Box 183)
  - Chicago, IL, 1961-1989 (Box 184, Folder 1-27)
  - Chicago, IL: Monthly Reports, 1957, 1959 (Box 184, Folder 28-29)
  - Chicago, IL, 1976, 1981-1982, 1984-1992, 1996-2009; 11 folders (Box 412)
  - Cleveland, IL, 1945-1948, 1952-1953 (Box 184, Folder 30-31)
  - Cleveland, IL, 1954-1987 (Box 184A, Folder 1-8)
  - Cleveland, OH, 1999-2003; 1 folder (Box 412)
  - Connecticut, 1953-1964 (Box 184A, Folder 9)
  - Denver, CO, 1976, 1980-1982 (Box 184A, Folder 10)
  - Detroit, MI, 1944-1953 (Box 184A, Folder 11-25)
  - Detroit, MI, 1954-1986 (Box 185, Folder 1-23)
  - Detroit, MI: Monthly Reports, 1956, 1967-1971 (Box 185, Folder 24-25)
  - Detroit, MI, 1976-1981, 1992-2008; 9 folders (Box 412)
  - Duluth, MN, 1954, 1958, 1961-1967 (Box 185, Folder 26-27)